{
	"data": [
    {
      "question": "He is waiting in the queue. Well _______ wait!",
      "a": "let he",
      "b": "let him",
      "c": "you let him",
      "d": "let you him",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb: Do it; Look at me",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Don't _______ do it.",
      "a": "let them",
      "b": "let they",
      "c": "you let them",
      "d": "you let they",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb: Do it; Look at me",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Here comes Jean, ______ to her!",
      "a": "speak not",
      "b": "don't let you speak",
      "c": "don't speak",
      "d": "don't speak you",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb: Do it; Look at me... \n- Negative: Don't + Base verb: Don't do it; Don't look at me",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Let _______ come with us.",
      "a": "them",
      "b": "they",
      "c": "them to",
      "d": "they to",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb: Do it; Look at me... \n+ Let somebody (us, me, her, them",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Come on, boys!_______ peace.",
      "a": "Have",
      "b": "Let's have",
      "c": "You have",
      "d": "Let have",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb: Do it; Look at me",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Carol, take this manuscript and ______ it, please.",
      "a": "you type",
      "b": "type you",
      "c": "type",
      "d": "let you type",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb: Do it; Look at me... \n+ You: is the common subject of all imperative sentences but often be hidden ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "She is coming to see you. All right,_______ come!",
      "a": "you let her",
      "b": "let you",
      "c": "let she",
      "d": "let her",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb: Do it; Look at me... \n+ You: is the common subject of all imperative sentences but often be hidden \n+ Let somebody (us, me, her, them",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "_______ be sensible about it!",
      "a": "Let we",
      "b": "Let us",
      "c": "We let be",
      "d": "Let we be",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb: Do it; Look at me... \n+ Let somebody (us, me, her, them",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "_______ go there today.",
      "a": "Don't let's not",
      "b": "Let we not",
      "c": "Let's not",
      "d": "Don't let we",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb: Do it; Look at me... \n- Let do something",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "I want to see Nora,______ come here at once!",
      "a": "let her",
      "b": "let she",
      "c": "tell her",
      "d": "tell she",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb: Do it; Look at me... \n- Let somebody do something",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "47",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "1"
    }
  ]
}